[Genius Girlfriend]
[Episode 19]
You're awake.
You seem to have a low fever.
Have some warm sugar water.
I can do it myself.
Let me.
It's just that
my blood sugar dropped.
Don't worry about me.
I'm going to get you something.
Is this
where you live?
Isn't it good here?
It's pretty cool.
So these are
what you usually eat?
Sometimes I'm too lazy to cook.
It's more convenient to eat these.
Have you...
Have you suffered a lot?
Nope.
I'm doing pretty well.
As a guy,
I don't care much about these things.
What do you do now?
I make handmade speakers for people.
Occasionally, there are also
some weird custom orders.
You could say I'm a craftsman.
Which school did you go to?
I have a self-taught diploma.
I won't mention the school.
It's not important in our industry anyway.
It's fine
as long as the work is done well.
What about me?
Why don't you ask how I'm doing?
You...
must be doing great.
You are Lin Zhixia.
I'm sure a bachelor's, Master's, or Ph.D
wouldn't be a problem for you.
You must be young
but highly respected at school.
Now you've
really grown into a young lady.
Then why have you never contacted us?
They are all so smart.
They must've gotten into good schools
and had great futures.
What about you?
What about yourself?
How have you been these past 5 years?
I...
I'm different from you guys.
You've been studying.
I've just been making a living.
You...
You know that's not what I want to hear.
You should have something to eat first.
Can we not talk about this
for now?
Jiang Yubai,
I just want to know
how you've been these past 5 years,
and what happened 5 years ago
that made you disappear all of a sudden.
None of us could find you.
Why did you hide from us?
I'm right in front of you now, aren't I?
Everything is exactly as you see it.
What's the point
of getting to the bottom of this?
Do you know that
you disappeared for 5 years?
For 5 whole years!
I've been looking for you
for 5 whole years!
It's been so long, Jiang Yubai!
Do you even see us as your friends?
What are we to you anyway?
You were looking for me.
Did I have to appear
just because you were looking for me?
Lin Zhixia,
you're not just a genius.
You are also like a sun.
Pure,
bright,
and shining.
You shine so brightly
and warm others.
But not everyone can keep shining forever,
just like you.
At least I can't.
But I've found you now.
We can face it together.
This world is really complicated.
There are dark places
where even your light can't reach.
I can help you.
How would you know?
You haven't even tried.
I don't need your help.
And you can't help me anyway.
This is my own business
and has nothing to do with you.
It has nothing to do with me?
Yes,
it does have nothing to do with me.
Then what does this watch
have to do with you?
Why did you fix it?
You had been hiding for 5 years!
Why did you show up now?
Why didn't you just keep hiding?
Yes!
Yeah, I shouldn't have fixed it.
I'm an idiot.
Are you happy now?
My biggest regret now is
ever fixing this stupid watch.
I should never have let you find me!
[Peng]
I have something to handle.
You should leave now.
You drove me away.
Fine.
I know you live here now.
You can't hide away anymore.
Look at you.
You're bold now, huh?
You even dare to reject my call.
I was outside just now
and couldn't answer.
But, Peng, I've paid this month's money.
I know.
I've never asked you for more.
But with the bank
raising interest rates now,
my rates are also going up.
So starting next month,
your interest will be increased by 3%.
Wait...
The interest rate was
already raised before.
And it's already pretty high.
If you raise it again,
won't it just become usury?
Jiang,
you can't say that.
When your mother's scandal
blew up back then,
with such a huge financial hole,
would any normal institution
have given you a loan?
If I hadn't reached out to help
because I thought you were young
and promising,
you'd still be hiding somewhere.
Got it? I was helping you
in your hour of need.
I'm also having a hard time now.
With inflation
and a bunch of bad debts out there
that can't be collected,
shouldn't you try to understand me a bit?
If you think
the interest rate is too high,
I have a solution.
I have a few games next week.
You come with me.
You're brainy.
Help me count cards,
and the interest will stay the same.
How's that?
Peng.
It is only natural to pay off debts.
I'll pay every bit of interest
I'm supposed to.
But I'm staying out of other stuff.
I can't help you with this.
Very well.
You've got some nerve.
Well, then, starting next month,
the interest rate will go up by 3%.
You shall pay every penny.
[Jiang Yubai]
[The alumni list of Nanhai No.1 High School
(mentions "Jiang Yubai")]
[The Star of Hope—Provincial Math Contest]
[Jiang Yubai won the first prize.]
[Local News]
[Master Jiang's Repair]
[Master Jiang fixed
my grandpa's military-merit radio.]
[He can listen to "Katyusha" once again.]
Master Jiang fixed
my grandpa's military-merit radio.
He can listen to "Katyusha" once again.
I saved up for 6 months
and finally got
Master Jiang's handmade speaker.
With sweet highs, accurate mids,
and powerful bass,
it beats factory products
in the 10,000-yuan range.
It's said that
Master Jiang was a legendary top student
who refused Qingbei University
despite lowered requirements.
Does anyone know why?
I can't figure it out.
Just forget it if you can't figure it out.
College students are a dime a dozen,
but craftsmen are scarce.
Isn't it good to have a mechanical genius?
They say
as long as you bring up a concept,
Master Jiang can make anything.
That's so amazing.
He's basically like a human 3D printer.
It's also said that he's very handsome
but very short of money.
Does anyone know why?
[He's excellent in mechanics, processing,
and adjustment. It's just reasonable.]
Cheng,
about Jiang Yubai...
I mean, Master Jiang.
I'd like to know
what he's been through these years.
Didn't I tell you to delete her contact?
Why do you still keep it?
Bro, I know your relationship.
But she's our client.
Of course, I have to keep it,
in case of after-sales service...
There is no after-sales service!
I won't take her orders!
Give me the phone.
Bro.
Give it to me!
[Miss Lin]
[Settings] [Delete Contact]
[Deleting the contact, "Miss Lin"]
[Loading]
[Settings]
Get out.
Okay.
I'll take my leave then.
Guess what I brought you.
This is from the restaurant
you said you really liked last time.
It was freshly made,
and I brought it over immediately
without delaying for a single minute.
Give it a try now.
I don't like it anymore lately.
I'm tired of it.
Tired of it?
Then what do you like to eat?
I'll bring it over to you right away.
Cut the small talk.
Just cut to the chase.
Well, um...
Tang.
Tingting.
Madam Tang, Miss Tang.
Look.
I have a shared e-bike company,
right?
It's called "Fun Biking."
This is it.
It needs a bit of promotion lately.
Well, we've known each other for years,
and we're old friends.
See if your company
has any suitable artists
whom you can help us
discuss a collaboration
or an endorsement with.
Our artists are very expensive.
That's exactly why I came to you!
Look.
Isn't our old classmates' friendship
worth a million or so?
Besides,
if we really make
our collaboration happen,
I will cover all the transportation needs
of your company.
Duan Qiyan, are you serious?
We are a talent agency!
What do we need your e-bikes for?
Do you expect our artists
to ride your e-bikes
to attend their work events?
Your employees
can ride them as well, right?
Hello?
Tingting,
I brought Mr. Wang
an iced Americano this afternoon.
He was so happy
and even helped me
refine my acting this afternoon.
You know what?
The directors all praised me today,
saying that I captured the emotions well,
and my eyes told the story.
Great job!
Keep it up.
Don't get cocky.
Tell me if anything happens.
Okay, I got it.
Tingting, I've got to go now.
They're calling me. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
"Great job!"
"Bye-bye."
Tang, not bad.
He is now
giving you real-time updates on his work.
That's why they say
kids always behave well.
Yeah,
He is well-behaved and sensible.
He follows my suggestions 100%,
so of course things turn out well.
Unlike you, Duan Qiyan.
How many suggestions
have I given you since we were little?
From choosing your college
to starting a business
with shared e-bikes,
have you ever listened
to a single piece of my advice?
You always do the opposite
and bicker with me.
Why should I listen to you?
Only a kid
who's still wet behind the ears like him
would listen to whatever you say.
I, Duan Qiyan,
am a man with my own ideas and opinions.
What's so great about getting resources
by sweet-talking women?
Then what did you come
to our company today?
Isn't it just that your own company
is struggling,
and you're here to piggyback on our fame?
Hey...
Duan Qiyan, listen.
Your acting is terrible.
Your fake flattery is so obvious.
Tang Tingting!
You...
Don't take it too far.
When have I, Duan Qiyan,
ever flattered anyone?
This is called win-win cooperation.
How could it be the same
as what that kid did?
Listen.
When I, Duan Qiyan,
look for a girlfriend in the future,
I will find someone
who's completely the opposite of you.
I'll find a woman
who's gentle, considerate,
obedient,
and submissive to me.
Like the exact inverse function
of someone like you!
Great, Duan Qiyan.
I wish you find your gentle
and considerate inverse function soon.
Now, take your great dream
and get out of here.
You want an endorsement?
No way!
Fine, whatever!
I'm not doing it anyway!
Stop being so pretentious.
You're tired of it?
Take it or leave it!
[Repayment plan for the next 3 months]
[437,000 yuan] [+39,330/3 months]
Master Jiang, have you eaten yet?
I brought you a pancake.
You really scared me yesterday.
Cheng.
Can we take more orders now?
You want even more orders?
No problem.
With your great reputation,
you can get as many as you want.
However,
won't that be too much for you physically?
Besides audio equipment,
I'll do any other work
for electronic devices,
smart home modifications,
or industrial controller repairs.
Master Jiang,
this is weird.
In view of your schedule,
are you planning
to burn yourself out in 3 months?
Why are you suddenly so fired up?
Is it because of that Miss Lin
at the door last time?
Did you two...
It has nothing to do with her.
Stop guessing.
Man...
You can fool others.
But you can hardly
fool me.
I saw everything last time.
She waited at the door
from dawn till dusk.
Also,
you texted me in such a panic,
telling me to send her away immediately.
She's obviously your ex-girlfriend.
Look,
you've been hiding
in this crappy warehouse for 5 years,
living like an ascetic monk.
You wouldn't even care about
a female cat passing by.
But why is it that she showed up
and suddenly you hid away and panicked?
You even made me
delete her WeChat contact yesterday.
Obviously, you still have
feelings for her,
yet you're too afraid to see her,
making yourself struggle
in a dilemma.
Am I right?
Cheng.
You still have a game console
waiting for a new chip here, right?
Leave right now
and don't come back
until you get me 10 orders,
or...
I happen to be short
of a few high-end capacitors,
which your game console
just happens to have.
Alright, Master Jiang.
I shouldn't have run my mouth.
I'm going to get you orders right now.
I promise you'll be soldering all day,
working your fingers to the bone.
Bye-bye.
[Repayment plan for the next 3 months]
[Go meet Lin Zhixia]
[Sensor Technology Lab]
Baihui.
Mom, Dad.
-Baihui.
What brings you here?
We're here to pick you up to...
Nothing.
I just missed you
and wanted to come to see you.
You look tired from studying.
We'll take you out for a nice meal tonight
for nutrition.
Okay.
Look at you, you've lost weight again.
How about we go to my dorm first,
so I can put away my things?
Okay, let's go.
Which way?
This way.
Mom, Dad, come in and rest for a bit.
So this is the grad student dorm?
Yeah.
It is different from the undergrad one.
The lighting is great.
I haven't had time to tidy up recently.
It's a bit messy. Have a seat first.
You live in such a big space alone?
My roommate just moved out,
and the new one hasn't moved in yet.
So you're basically
living in a single room.
Yeah.
It's fine.
Studying is the priority.
Baihui.
You can't spend all your time studying.
You still need
to have a life.
I'm used to it.
Studying isn't tiring for me.
That won't do.
You need to get along well
with your classmates
and make more friends.
You might not see it at school,
but once you graduate and enter society,
you'll realize the importance of friends.
Okay.
Speaking of your classmates,
do you guys interact
with the philosophy department?
The philosophy department
doesn't have much interaction with us.
I'm not familiar with them.
I heard about a guy named Li Zhe.
He's good at his studies
and comes from a good family.
Have you ever heard of him?
I don't know him.
Baihui.
Let me just be straight with you.
Do you remember
when your dad and I video-called you,
and there were two madams with us?
One of them
is Li Zhe's mother.
She said Li Zhe had
a really good impression of you.
We're having dinner with them today.
Yes, we're having dinner together.
So we're eating with them today?
Just for you to get to know each other.
By the way...
I also bought you a dress.
Look.
It's pretty.
This really brings out your vibe.
Change into it later, okay?
Alright, Jin.
Let's go first and let her get ready.
Okay.
I happen to have a paper to submit.
I'll go in a bit.
Okay.
Don't be late.
Put on some makeup.
See you later.
[Xinrong Wealth's scandal was exposed.
Its legal representative is on the run.]
Hello, Mom.
Did you eat?
Yes, I did.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just want to confirm something with you.
[Xinrong Wealth's scandal was exposed.
Its legal representative is on the run.]
That P2P online lending product
we bought before...
I mean the one
Jiang Yubai's mom sold.
How did it end up?
Did they provide compensation?
Oh, that thing.
Yes, they did compensate.
But we were lucky.
We got all our principal back.
The interest was gone for sure.
I heard many people
didn't even get their principal back.
It was so miserable.
Is it called Xinrong Wealth?
Let me think.
Yes, that's it.
Why the sudden question?
Did you run into something?
Are you short of money?
No.
I just saw a similar case
on the news,
so I asked.
Okay.
I won't keep you any longer.
Zhixia, you must tell us
if something happens.
Bye.
[Xinrong Wealth's scandal was exposed.
Its legal representative is on the run.]
He's basically like a human 3D printer.
It's also said that he's very handsome
but very short of money.
Does anyone know why?
Sorry, I'm late.
Baihui, come here.
Hello, Baihui.
-Have a seat.
-Hello, madam.
Sit down.
Baihui,
I heard you're so busy with your studies,
yet you made a special trip here.
It's nothing.
Actually,
we don't want her to spend all her time
studying at school either.
Baihui,
this is Li Zhe,
your senior
from the philosophy department.
Nice to meet you.
Baihui,
Li Zhe always talks about you at home
with his dad and me,
saying that you're an excellent student
with a calm personality.
We've finally met you today.
You really are a wonderful girl.
Thank you.
This is also my first time meeting Li Zhe.
He's also
a handsome gentleman.
Everyone, let's eat up.
Baihui, have as much as you want.
Okay.
Li Zhe, take care of Baihui.
By the way,
Jin.
Li wanted to come back today.
Thank you.
But he suddenly got called into a meeting.
He told me to apologize to you
and said he'd treat you
to a meal next time.
Do you have any hobbies
besides studying?
I don't have many hobbies.
Like me, I prefer outdoor sports
and making friends
with like-minded people.
We can have fun together
if there's a chance.
I probably won't have much spare time.
Look at Baihui.
The more I look at her,
the more I like her.
You've also raised Li Zhe so well.
Look, he's also studying
at Qingbei University.
Both of them are students
Yeah.
In the future,
their children will definitely
be even more excellent.
From now on,
we'll be one family.
I won't treat you as outsiders.
I'll take care
of them.
Don't worry.
-Don't just talk. Come on, eat up.
-Since you're usually so busy,
did you date anyone in college?
Pardon?
I mean, dating.
Sorry,
I'm just
a straightforward person.
If I said something that upset you,
I didn't mean to.
It's fine.
I think you have
a really good personality.
You are steadier than I am.
If we are together someday,
maybe
the family social things
could be left to you.
I think you'd do a better job than me.
Once Baihui marries into our family,
you can rest assured.
You don't need to worry about anything.
Just leave it all to me.
I'll take care of it.
Let them focus on their work.
Leave their children to me as well.
I'll take care of everything.
Come on, cheers.
Let them get to know each other first.
Yes,
let them get to know each other first.
Okay.
-Come on.
-Cheers.
You probably don't drink, do you?
Let's use tea
instead of wine
to make a toast to your parents
and my mom later.
After all, they've done so much
for the two of us.
As the younger generation,
we should show our appreciation.
Um, excuse me.
I'm going to use the restroom.
Let's enjoy the meal first.
Eat more, Li Zhe.
Okay.
You're too thin.
[Tried to manually track
the shadow changes]
[in craters around Oceanus Procellarum
on the moon.]
[The observation was
a bit clearer than last time.]
[Lin Zeqiu]
[Tried to manually track
the shadow changes]
[in craters around Oceanus Procellarum
on the moon.]
[The observation was
a bit clearer than last time.]
[Lin Zeqiu] [Friend Profile]
[Lin Zeqiu] [Moments]
[Tried to manually track
the shadow changes]
[in craters around Oceanus Procellarum
on the moon.]
[The observation was
a bit clearer than last time.]
[Lin Zeqiu]
[Why hide the sun?]
[Lin Zeqiu] [Industry Exchange Session]
[Count me in
next time you photograph stars.]
[Lin Zeqiu] [Industry Exchange Session]
[Why didn't you photograph stars today?
How's the sky?]
Why didn't you photograph stars today?
How's the sky?
I was too busy
to do it today.
You can look up and see for yourself.
[Lin Zeqiu]
[Repayment plan for the next 3 months]
[Jiang Yubai, it's time for you
to repay the money this month, right?]
[Calling]
[Hang up]
[Jiang Yubai, it's time for you
to repay the money this month, right?]
Peng, I already paid the money this month.
You came to the workshop
to collect it last Wednesday.
[Oh, yes. There are too many loans.
I mixed them up.]
[Jiang Yubai, it's time for you
to repay the money this month, right?]
[Peng, I already
paid the money this month.]
[You came to the workshop
to collect it last Wednesday.]
[Oh, yes. There are too many loans.
I mixed them up.]
[Notes]
[Online Banking Electronic Receipt]
[Repayment Record] [Recipient: Peng]
[Notes]
[Online Banking Electronic Receipt]
[Transfer to Peng: 19,280 yuan]
[Repayment Record] [Recipient: Peng]
♪ With every breath, the shadows creep ♪
[Online Banking Electronic Receipt]
[Repayment Record] [Recipient: Peng]
♪ A demon in disguise ♪
[Online Banking Electronic Receipt]
[Repayment Record] [Recipient: Peng]
♪ Talking the sweetest lies ♪
[Online Banking Electronic Receipt]
♪ It tries to drown me in my sleep ♪
[Repayment Record] [Recipient: Peng]
[Online Banking Electronic Receipt]
♪ Pain comes like a tide ♪
[Repayment Record] [Recipient: Peng]
♪ It hurts,
but I'm way too tired to hide ♪
3.28 million.
♪ Will you please hold me, help me
walk out of this endless night ♪
3.28 million.
♪ I've lost my light and power ♪
♪ Lost my will to fight ♪
[Total transfer amount
over the past 5 years: 3,287,650 yuan]
♪ Will you stand by my side ♪
♪ Be my light tonight ♪
♪ Let's run away ♪
♪ Embrace the light ♪
♪ With you, I'll win this fight ♪
♪ Let's run away ♪
♪ No time to cry ♪
♪ Your love will guide us
through the night ♪
♪ Let's run away ♪
♪ No time to cry ♪
♪ Your love will guide us
through the night ♪
♪ You and I ♪
♪ Endless night ♪
Jiang Yubai.
I've finally...
♪ I feel alive ♪
I've finally found you.